[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Продавати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'Знати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しります"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Проживати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すみます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Досліджувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんきゅうします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Документ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しりょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Розклад' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じこくひょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Холостяк' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "どくしん"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Перукарня (чоловіча)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とこや"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Салон краси, перукарня (жіноча)' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "びよういん"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Власну' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じぶん"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Театральна каса' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "プレイガイド"
    }
]
